我和我的兄弟姊妹是历史上
最早的吸血鬼
KLAUS: My siblings and I
are the first vampires in history.
是真祖家族
The Originals.
三百年前，我们帮助建立了纽奥良
Three hundred years ago,
we helped build New Orleans.
我们不在的时候，一个新的国王崛起了
In our absence, a new king arose.
现在我重回这里，将他的王国占为己有
Now, I've returned and
taken his kingdom as my own.
我曾希望这能让我的家族团结一致
I had hoped this would
bring our family together.
但我错了
I was wrong.
我想夺回我们的家
所以我要去那里生活
I wanted our home back,
so I'm going to live there,
你们两个
就一起待在这里慢慢腐烂吧
and the two of you,
you can stay here together and rot.
你跟我走，小狼
You're coming with me, little wolf.
我干嘛要跟你走？
Why would I go anywhere with you?
你可以反抗我，但你赢不了我
You can fight me on this,
but you will lose.
任何想阻止你上车的人也赢不了我
As will anyone else who tries
to stop you getting in this car.
首先，让我们举杯
敬我们共有的恩赐，永生
Let us begin with a toast
to our shared gift, immortality.
一千年后
After 1,000 years,
你们也许会以为生活会感觉不那么强烈
one might expect for life
to be less keenly felt,
因为随着时间
生活的美丽与哀愁会减弱
for its beauties and
its sorrows to diminish with time.
但身为吸血鬼
But as vampires,
我们的感受是人类难以想像地深刻
we feel more deeply than
humans could possibly imagine.
永不满足的需求
剧烈的痛苦
Insatiable need, exquisite pain.
这是我们的胜利
也是我们的失败
Our victories, and our defeats.
没时间安抚你受伤的自尊心了
You can't afford your wounded pride.
克劳斯掌控着你的帝国
With Klaus in control of your empire,
你得给他他最渴望得到的东西
忠诚
you need to give him
what he craves most, loyalty.
或者至少给他忠诚的错觉
Or at least the illusion of it.
我埋伏了他，试图将他活埋
I ambushed him,
tried to bury him alive.
他再也不会信任我了
He's not going to trust me.
他会的，因为他想得到你的效忠
He will because he wants
your allegiance.
以往的经验让我明白
如果你表现出忠诚
Speaking from experience,
I know that if you play the part,
没什么不能原谅的
但如果你给了他任何理由去怀疑你
all is forgiven. But if you
give him any reason to doubt you,
他就会反击
he will strike back.
答应我，马赛尔
Make me a promise, Marcel.
你要不惜一切代价活下去
You do whatever it takes
to stay alive.
敬我的城市，这里又成为我的家园
To my city, my home again.
愿鲜血永不停止流动
May the blood never cease to flow.
愿派对永不结束
And the party never end.
我不明白，兄弟
MAN: I just don't get it, man.
你知道我们会支持你直到最后
You know we would've stood
with you till the end.
那么做只会害死你们
Letting you do that
would've been letting you die,
而你们仍是我的人
and you're still my people.
现在，听我的指挥就好
For now, just follow my lead.
相信我，这还没完呢
Trust me, it ain't over yet.
敬纽奥良
To New Orleans.
- 敬纽奥良
- 纽奥良
-To New Orleans.
-ALL: New Orleans.
我明白你们有些人也许会对最近
I understand that some
of you may have questions
领导者的变动心存疑惑
regarding the recent change
in leadership,
我今晚邀请你们来是向你们解释清楚
and I invited you here
tonight to assure you
你们不是被打败了
that you are not defeated.
不是，我下一步打算
就是庆祝我们所拥有的
No. My intentions moving forward
are to celebrate what we have.
实际上是马赛尔夺走
What Marcel, in fact, took...
并建立形成的
...and built into this;
一个真正的吸血鬼社区
a true community of vampires.
那她呢，这个狼人？
What about her, the wolf?
让我说完，迪亚哥
你知道
Had you let me finish, Diego,
you would know that
当然还有另外一件事我要解释
there is, of course, one further
matter I would like to address.
你们许多人都知道
这女孩怀了我的孩子
As many of you know,
the girl is carrying my child.
因此，我相信
你们都会给她应有的尊重
Consequently, I trust you will
all pay her the appropriate respect.
然而，我知道你们有些人很关心
However, I understand that
some of you are concerned
那个恶毒的传闻
by this vicious rumor...
说我想要利用孩子的血
制造混合种
...that I intend to use the blood
of our child to create Hybrids.
我向你们保证，我不会这么做
I assure you, I do not.
年度最佳父亲
Father of the year.
显然我得赢得你们的信任
It appears I will have
to earn your trust.
很好
Very well.
我们会消除你们焦虑的根源
We'll eliminate the root
of your anxiety.
你们想想，如果河口
没有任何活着的狼人
You see, how can I sire any Hybrids
我还怎么制造出混合种呢？
if there are no more werewolves
alive in the bayou to turn?
什么？克劳斯，不行
What? Klaus, no.
所以，尽情吃喝，尽情欢乐
So eat, drink, and be merry,
而明天
我建议你们去猎猎狼人
and tomorrow I suggest you have
yourselves a little wolf hunt.
去吧，开心一下
Go ahead. Have fun.
杀光他们
Kill them all.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）
剧名：统御之痛
绝对不行，我付过钱了
Absolutely not.
I paid for that.
拜托
Please.
千万不要为任何东西付出代价
主演：约瑟夫摩根
You never paid
for anything in your life.
我看不出这有什么关系
主演：约瑟夫摩根
I hardly see how that's relevant.
尼克在惩罚我们
Nik is just punishing us.
我们伤害了他
Well, we've hurt him deeply,
看起来伤得还很深
主演：丹尼尔吉利斯
it would appear.
每当我们以为
已经见识到他最坏的一面
We believed the worst about him
the one time in a million
却一次又一次发现那都不是真的
主演：克莱儿荷特
when the worst
wasn't actually the truth.
你要去哪？
Where do you think you're going?
确保海莉没有因为我们的错误而受罪
To ensure that Hayley
doesn't suffer for our mistakes.
主演：菲比托金
尼克劳斯现在正怀恨在心
If Niklaus is feeling vindictive,
我们不能相信她是安全的
主演：查尔斯麦可戴维斯
we cannot trust that she is safe.
所以我咬了以利亚
把他留在河口
So, then I bit Elijah,
and left him in the bayou
任我混合种的毒液在他血管中流窜
主演：丹妮耶拉皮纳达
with my Hybrid venom in his veins.
让他为那些卑鄙的指控付出代价
主演：莉雅派普斯
Serves him right for making such
vile accusations against me.
然后
And then...
你在记录吗？
Are you taking this down?
先说清楚，如果法语区现在是你的
主演：丹妮儿坎贝尔
To be clear,
if the Quarter is yours now,
你为什么还需要我呢？
you still need me why?
我的回忆录
My memoirs.
一千年的历史又不会自己写出来
A thousand years of history
isn't going to write itself.
卡蜜，你在这里做什么？
Cami, what are you doing here?
我也想问
My question exactly.
没关系的，她知道
Oh, it's quite all right.
She knows.
- 她知道了？
- 知道你们是吸血鬼吗？
-She does?
-That you're vampires?
别担心，他已经魅惑我
一离开就会忘记这一切
Don't worry. He's compelled me to
forget everything as soon as I leave.
那样的话，我就忙着苦恼
我到底是不是疯了
That way, I'm too busy agonizing over
whether or not I'm losing
而不会意识到我在为一个
长生不死的自大狸做间谋
my damn mind to realize I'm playing
spy for an immortal egomaniac.
你魅惑她和我约会，是不是？
You compelled her to go
out with me, didn't you?
我以为你是真的喜欢我
And I thought you really liked me.
我也这么以为
So did l.
先说清楚
我只是魅惑你让你给他个机会
Well, to be clear, I only
compelled you to give him a chance.
你对他的感觉都是真的
Anything you felt
for him was quite real.
制片：兰斯安德森
再声明一下
And, for the record,
我们现在感受到的这种尴尬
the level of awkwardness
we're all currently experiencing
完全是真实的
is entirely genuine.
你自以为很聪明，是吗？
You think you're so clever,
don't you,
魅惑一个可怜天真的酒保
compelling the poor,
naive bartender?
看看我发现了什么
真实的我，不是你魅惑的治疗师
Look what I found,
real me, not your compelled therapist.
实际上
我更喜欢称你为敬业的速记员
Well, actually I prefer
devoted stenographer.
你觉得扰乱我的心智很有趣吗？
You think this is funny,
messing with my mind?
我的理智可不是什么玩笑
My sanity is not a joke.
不，亲爱的，我也认为不是
No, love, I don't believe it is.
你从来没有发现这张照片
You never found this.
你离开这里以后就会忘记
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
You will remember nothing of our life
我们是吸血鬼的所有事情
制片：朗恩麦克劳德
as vampires when you leave here.
明白了吗？
Do you understand?
我想今天就到这里吧
I think that just about
does it for the day.
你可以走了
You may go.
想去哪吗？
Going somewhere?
以利亚
Elijah.
你不该来这里
克劳斯派他的手下盯着我
You shouldn't be here.
Klaus has his guys watching me.
我倒不担心他们
-I wouldn't worry about them.
-(GRUNTlNG)
走吧，我们不能逗留太久
我们替你找个安全的地方
Come. We mustn't linger.
Let's get you someplace safe.
不，你不用担心我，我很好
编剧：艾胥莉莱尔，巴特尼克森
No. You don't have to
worry about me. I'm fine.
我现在在万能克劳斯的保护下
I've been deemed under protection
by the almighty Klaus.
我现在在万能克劳斯的保护下
导演：乔许巴特勒
I've been deemed under protection
by the almighty Klaus.
那些狼人才需要帮助
导演：乔许巴特勒
It's the werewolves who need help.
为了向马赛尔那群人示好
He ordered a wolf hunt
as some jacked-up peace offering
他发起了对狼人的猎杀行动
to Marcel's crew.
- 你们一定要帮帮他们
- 在河口吗？
-You have to help them.
-Out in the bayou?
我们看起来像吸血鬼救援小队吗？
Do we look like a bloody
vampire rescue squad?
我们能来救你你就该感恩了
I think you should be grateful
we came to save you.
听着，蕾贝卡，我这一生
Listen, Rebekah.
All my life,
都在寻找我真正的家人
I've wanted to know
who my real family was,
我才刚发现他们在河口
and just as I find out that
they're out there in the bayou,
克劳斯就下令要杀了他们
Klaus orders them killed.
你们想帮我？
You want to help me?
那就帮帮我的族人
求求你们
Help my people, please.
人类召开了会议
Humans have called a meeting.
他们对现状不太满意
They're not exactly thrilled
with the new status quo.
那真是遗憾
How unfortunate for them.
现在是你出马的时候了
MARCEL: Look. It's your show now,
但你如果想知道我如何建立这个帝国
那就是政治
but you want to know
how I built what I built? Politics.
一点点交际手腕就能让你走很远
这招尤其对人类管用
A little diplomacy goes a long way,
especially with the human faction.
明白了
Duly noted.
我已经很久没回想起那晚的事了
I haven't thought about
this night in ages.
1919年，旧歌剧院被烧毁之前
1919, the Opera House
just before it burned.
这是一个时代的终结
This was the end of an era.
为了有个崭新的开始
Now, in the interest
of new beginnings,
我觉得我需要向你坦白些事情
I feel there are some things
I should probably confess to you.
但从哪里说起呢？
But where to begin?
提艾里从来没有背叛过你
Thierry was never disloyal to you.
为了找到我哥哥，我陷害了他
I set him up in an attempt
to locate my brother.
既然他是你朋友
He's your friend,
and consequently,
如果你想的话，他可以回来
he can return to the compound
at your discretion.
卡蜜的事你也知道了
还有约书亚那小伙子
Cami's part you just learned,
and then there's young Joshua.
我一开始就魅惑他了
I've been compelling him
from the beginning,
但我想你已经知道了
although I suspect you
already knew that,
毕竟是他让我掉入了你的陷阱
as he was the one who
led me into your trap.
我好像告诉过他一些错误的讯息
I may have fed the kid
some misinformation.
还有黛维娜
And then there's Davina.
她是个强大的武器
She's a powerful weapon.
眼下，我希望她能随时待命
At this point,
I'd like to keep her close at hand.
我认为我们应该让她
搬来和我们一起住
I think we should have her move
into the compound here with us.
她不能离开阁楼
我曾经试图带她走
She can't leave the attic.
I already tried to move her once.
是的，关于那件事，事实上
你的小女巫演技真的不错
Yes. About that, turns out
your little witch is quite the actress.
她和被囚禁的以利亚做了一个交易
She made a deal with Elijah
while he was in captivity,
骗你让她留在那里
tricked you into letting her stay put
以换取我母亲魔法书中的一些咒语
in exchange for some spells
from our mother's grimoire.
多谢你告诉我
Good to know.
还有吗？
Is that all?
应该就这些了
I do believe it is.
感谢你的开诚布公
Appreciate the honesty.
嗯
Ah.
会议安排在一小时后
Meeting is in an hour.
（不要相信克劳斯告诉你的任何事）
（手提包的内袋）
所以我咬了以利亚
(BEEPS)
KLAUS' VOlCE: So, then I bit Elijah,
把他留在河口
任我混合种的毒液在他血管中流窜
and left him in the bayou with
my Hybrid venom in his veins.
让他为那些卑鄙的指控付出代价
Serves him right for making
such vile accusations against me.
你一定会喜欢那地方的
You're going to love it
at the compound.
我已经为你挑选了那里最好的房间
I already got the best room
in the place picked out.
我不能离开
记得上次发生的事情吗？
I can't leave.
Remember what happened last time?
我知道你和以利亚的交易了
I know about your deal with Elijah.
我们不能对彼此撒谎
We can't be lying to each other.
我在试图保护你
那些女巫为了收种祭
I'm trying to protect you.
With the witches still looking
还会试图杀了你
相信我，你和我们在一起最安全
to kill you for the Harvest,
believe me, you're safest with us.
而且那里午后的阳光很棒
Plus, there's excellent light
in the afternoon.
看来你是个艺术家
I see you're an artist.
太好了
Wonderful.
我很期待欣赏你的各种才华
I look forward to
witnessing your many talents.
这是他的主意吗？
Was this his idea?
黛维娜，别这样
Davina, please.
我明白你效忠于马赛尔
I understand
you're devoted to Marcel,
但马赛尔效忠于我
but Marcel is devoted to me.
我觉得你也想让大家都好吧
I assume you want
what's best for all of us.
我们要下楼开会了
We have a meeting
to attend downstairs.
我会派人来收拾你的东西
Look. I'll get someone
to pick up your things.
我们会把你安顿好的
We'll get you settled in right.
相信我
Trust me.
克劳斯，马赛尔，感谢你们前来
Klaus, Marcel, thank you for coming.
我们获悉了最近在你们群体中
领导权的变动
We are aware of the change
in leadership in your community,
我们想是时候做正式的介绍了
and we thought it was time to make
the appropriate introductions.
我们希望你能明白这里的规矩
We want to be sure you understand
how things work around here.
是吗？
Is that so?
市长的意思是
What the Mayor means
我们只是想确认一下最近的变化
is that we just want some assurance
that this new development
不会威胁到我们的城市和居民
isn't going to endanger
our city or its inhabitants.
听着，你们这帮怪物做些什么
我们就当作不知道
Look, you freaks do your thing,
and we'll look the other way.
只要我们的利益不受损失
我们不会有任何异议
As long as our pockets stay full,
we won't have a problem.
更重要的是，有些规矩需要遵守
More importantly, there are rules.
不能吸本地人的血
No feeding on the locals.
不要让城市引来不必要的关注
Don't bring any unwanted
attention to the city.
历史证明我们可以和平共处
History has proven that
we can coexist peacefully.
- 但如果你们侵犯了底线…
- 就要对我们有个交代
-However, if you cross the line--
-You answer to us.
好吧，不好意思
让我理清一下头绪
(LAUGHlNG) Okay. I'm sorry.
Let me get this straight.
在这个自大狂
和他手下这群可笑的小偷面前
I'm to play supplicant
to this pompous ass
我要表现得卑躬屈膝吗？
and his ridiculous group
of petty thieves?
我的条件是这样的
Here are my terms.
你会得到我认为合适的施舍
You will take whatever scraps
I see fit to leave you,
并且感激不尽
and you will be grateful.
如果你有任何不满
If that doesn't suit you,
或许我会认为你就没有活着的价值了
I may decide
you've outlived your usefulness.
他们显然刚刚还在这
Hey, they were obviously just here.
分头去找，找到他们后，提头来见
Fan out, find them,
and bring me some heads.
我劝你别这么做
I'd rather you didn't.
你们来这干什么？
What the hell are
you doing out here?
我是来建议你另寻他处进行狩猎
I've come to suggest you seek
other hunting grounds.
这建议我听到了
Suggestion noted.
迪亚哥，这么帅气的脸蛋
Now, Diego,
it would be such a shame
被伤了岂不可惜？
to have to rearrange
that pretty face.
你们怎么会在乎狼人的死活？
What the hell you care about wolves?
一般来说，我毫不在乎
Generally, I don't.
但唯独这支狼族你们动不得
However, this particular
clan is not to be touched.
再见
Goodbye.
Bye.
反正这里什么也没有
Nothing here, anyway.
好极了，我想我们的任务完成了
Great.
I guess our job here is done.
还没有
Not quite.
我们不是来伤害你的
We're not here to harm you.
又见面了
Hello, again.
你叫伊芙，对吧？
Eve, was it?
你就是海莉的小亲友之一吧
One of Hayley's litter-mates, I presume.
是海莉叫你们来保护我们的，对吧？
Hayley sent you here to protect us,
didn't she?
请转告她我们感谢她的关心
Tell her we appreciate the concern,
但我们一直以来都能照顾自己
but we've been looking out
for ourselves for a while now.
除非我们自愿现身
否则没人能找到我们
Nobody finds us
unless we want to be found.
我们这不就找到你了吗？所以…
Well, we found you, so...
正如我所说…
Like I said...
我想有些事情
你和你的家族都需要知道
There's something I thought you
and your family should know about.
我觉得我对他们已经很仁慈了
I think I was far more gracious
than they deserved.
你对我的交际手段感到失望
You're disappointed
by my lack of diplomacy.
我想，最不需要他人提醒
Well, you, above all people,
人类有多残忍的就是你了
should need no reminder of
the human capacity for cruelty.
喂？
Hello?
米卡森先生
只想知会你一声
MAN: Mr. Mikaelson,
just wanted to let you know,
我们已考虑过你的条件
the faction has
considered your terms.
我们达成了一致的决定
We've reached a decision.
是吗？
Have you?
该死，该死，该死！
Damn it, damn it, damn it!
这都是你的错
This is on you.
现在主事的人是你
这里死的都是你的人
Now that you're in charge,
those are your guys laying dead.
你的人
Your guys.
如果你想掌管这座城市
就不能视手下的生死于无物
If you're going to run this city,
that better mean something to you.
否则没有任何有能之士
会愿意效忠于你，谁也不会
Otherwise no one worth a damn
is going to follow you, no one.
我之前还有点担心你呢
I was beginning to worry about you.
我都快受不了你这副
假装恭敬顺从的模样了
I don't think I could've taken any
more of this deferential nonsense.
显然，是我低估了那帮人类
I mean, clearly,
I underestimated the faction.
下不为例，但请告诉我
如今事情发展到这种地步
That won't happen again. But tell me,
now that we've arrived at this point,
如今他们胆敢闯进我们的家
now that they have come
into our home,
伤害我们的人
visited this upon our people...
你认为我该如何反击呢？
How would you counsel
me to respond?
把他们杀个片甲不留
Let's go kill them all.
这周围有两万亩的沼泽
We're surrounded
by 20,000 acres of swamp.
在这长大的狼人对地形了如指掌
The ones born here know it
like the backs of our hands.
我们不会有事，但这一带
有从别处来的狼人
We'll be fine, but here,
newcomers from out of state,
他们与海莉和我们并非同族
但关于她孩子的消息传开了
not Hayley's and my kin,
but word spread about that baby of hers.
很多狼人想亲眼见证
这次奇迹般的妊娠
A lot of werewolves want to see this
miracle pregnancy for themselves.
但如今吸血鬼要把狼人赶尽杀绝
Only now the vampires
are out looking for blood,
河口这些初来乍到的狼人
他们也许不知道该藏身于何处
and all these werewolves new to the
bayou, might not know where to hide.
你说得好像我们应该在乎一样
You say that
like we're supposed to care.
相信我，你们不会想让他们死的
Believe me, you're going
to want them kept alive.
为什么？
And why is that?
你们自己去看看吧
See for yourself.
我知道你在这，小约
I know you're in here, Josh.
我能感觉到你的恐惧
I can sense your fear.
听说你搬进来住了
I heard you were moving in.
你在这里干嘛？
What are you doing in here?
我在躲避追杀啊
试图隐姓埋名
Uh, you know, I'm hiding out.
You know, incognito.
本来得没命地逃跑
但直到天黑前我都得被困在这
Got to run for the hills,
but I'm stuck here until it gets dark.
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
很好啊，没事
Yeah, yeah.
不，其实一点都不好
我把克劳斯引进了一个陷阱中
No, not really. I mean,
I totally led Klaus into a trap
这该是史上最大的错误了
that was like the most
epic fail of all time.
所以我现在吓得都快尿裤子了
So, yeah, I'm kind of crapping
my pants right now,
只是个比喻，目前而言
figuratively... so far.
没事的
你可以相信马赛尔
It's okay.
You can trust Marcel.
而且如果克劳斯试图伤害你
我不会放过他
And if Klaus tries to hurt you,
I'll hurt him.
我敢肯定，要是你真能阻止克劳斯
I'm sure if you
could actually stop Klaus,
一定早就动手了
you would've done it already.
你是海莉，克劳斯的妻子
You're Hayley, Klaus' wife.
不是，才不要嫁给他呢
Ew. No. Never.
我是那个怀孕的狼人
I'm the pregnant werewolf,
想必你就是那个法力强大的
超级女巫黛维娜
and you must be the all-powerful
super witch Davina.
还有小约
不自量力的菜鸟吸血鬼
And let's not forget Josh,
newbie vampire way out of his element,
公认的下一个最有可能惨死的人
voted most likely to die next.
太棒了
Oh, fantastic.
我也是克劳斯的囚犯
Hey, I'm just another
one of Klaus' prisoners.
当然，如果让他发现
你还偷偷摸摸地藏身在此
Of course,
it would suck if he found out
就糟糕了
you were still lurking around.
也许我们可以
共同合作，相互照顾
Maybe there's a world
where we can all look out for each other.
我几小时前就打给你了
I called you hours ago!
我尽快赶来了
I came as fast as I could.
发生什么事了？
你的留言听起来…
What's going on?
Your voicemail sounded...
怎样？偏执多疑，精神错乱吗？
What, paranoid, unhinged?
不安
Upset.
我找到的那张照片
那张…我也不知道
That picture I found,
the one that was, I don't know,
大概有一百年历史的老照片
a hundred years old,
你说这只是巧合，但是…
you said it was
just a coincidence, but...
我的理智可不是什么玩笑
(BEEPS)
CAMl (VOlCE): My sanity is not a joke.
不，亲爱的，我也认为不是
KLAUS (VOlCE):
No, love, I don't believe it is.
那是我的声音，但我不记得说过这话
That's my voice,
but I don't remember it.
我觉得这…这可能是
精神控制之类的把戏
I think it's... I think it's
some kind of mind control.
我觉得他消除了我的记忆
(CELL PHONE RlNGlNG)
I think he's erasing my memory!
喂？
Yes?
他们干了什么？
They what?
这事我们以后再谈
We will talk about this later.
为什么没人跟我商量？
Why wasn't I consulted on this?
你离开了八个多月，基兰
You've been gone
for over eight months, Kieran.
我们已经习惯了依靠自己
We got used to
doing things on our own.
这个克劳斯米卡森
This Klaus Mikaelson,
不管他是谁，谣言怎么传
I don't care who he is
or what the rumors say.
他应该受点教训
He needed to be taught a lesson.
你们会引发战争的
You are going to start a war.
他们有种就试试
I'd like to see them try.
对了，基兰
这是你最后一次召集我们
Oh, and Kieran, this is the
last time you call a meeting.
下次你再想批评我们的领导能力
请发电子邮件
Next time you want to criticize our
leadership, send a damn email.
我以为这次会议是你们召集的
I thought you called this meeting.
是我们才怪
The hell we did.
其实是我安排的
KLAUS: Actually, I called it.
看来之前与各位见面时
我犯了一个严重的错误
It appears I made a grave error
during our earlier conference.
我朋友马赛尔给了我明智的建议
而我却充耳不闻
My friend Marcel offered me wise counsel,
and I failed to heed it.
你吸取了教训，我很欣慰
Well, I'm glad to hear
you've learned your lesson.
是啊，我不会再犯那种错误了
Oh, I won't be making
that mistake again.
马赛尔？
Marcel?
开始吧
Shall we?
你先请
After you.
看看他
唯一的幸存者
There he is, our lone survivor.
这个城市今天很不幸啊
Such a sad day for our city.
几位头脑聪明的精英
Some of its best and brightest
在密西西比河上过到悲惨事故丧生
killed in a tragic boating
accident on the Mississippi.
听说是很严重的爆炸
Rather nasty explosion, I heard.
我要怎么处置你呢？
What am I going to do with you?
好，先等等
Okay. Hold up.
我认识基兰很久了
I've known Kieran for a long time.
他很聪明，也很公正
He's smart, and he's fair.
他活着对我们更有好处
He can do us more good
alive than dead.
再说他还是卡蜜的叔叔
Not to mention he's Cami's uncle.
你平时什么都不在乎
Don't see you care about much.
所以一旦在乎了，很容易看得出来
It's kind of hard not
to notice when you do.
很好
Very well.
利用这次机会
重建你们这群人类小团体吧
Use this reprieve
to remake your human faction.
我要怎么重新找一个市长啊？
And how do you expect
me to remake the mayor?
应该有副市长吧
Well, surely
there's a deputy mayor.
换一批领导人
我们再进行谈判
Choose new leaders,
then we reopen negotiations.
这群狼人旅行还是很讲究的，不是吗？
Wow, these wolves really
travel in style, don't they?
空的
Empty.
大概是没付租金吧
Behind on their payments, perhaps.
要继续找吗？
Shall we proceed then?
不要了，然后跟海莉说都找过了
Let's not and tell
Hayley that we did.
那样你让她对你有了好感
我也可以回家了
Then you get to impress the girl,
and I can go home.
你知道我不喜欢小屋的
You know how hovels depress me.
我不是要让她对我有好感
I'm not trying to impress the girl.
我真希望你是呢
不然我们来这里干什么啊？
I should bloody hope you are.
Why else are we out here?
得了吧，以利亚
Come on, Elijah.
你喜欢上她了，承认吧
You've fallen for her.
Admit it.
承认了之后也许
你长久以来的骄傲和闷骚
May do wonders for the stick
that's lodged up your
就可以解脱了
enduringly stoic ass if you did.
我只能说，这事很复杂
这样可以吗
If I admit to you that
it's complicated, would that suffice?
还是说你一定要逼我说得一清二楚？
Or are you determined to torment me
throughout this endeavor?
亲爱的，我们不能总是这样见面
Darling, we have to stop
meeting like this.
流言就是这么来的
This is how rumors begin.
你可以走了
You can go now.
该死
Damn it!
也许我说得不够清楚
Perhaps I'm not
making myself clear here.
我在威胁你
This is a threat.
给你三分钟，不然你的这群猎人
In precisely three minutes time,
your little hunting party
会变成猎物
will become the prey.
基于你连我弟弟尼克劳斯都打不过
Now, based on your recent failure
to subdue my baby brother Niklaus,
你再不顺从，会输得很惨
this despite a better
than 100 to one advantage...
奉劝你把我的警告听进去
...I recommend you heed my warning.
不错嘛
Impressive.
我还以为刚才的情势
要动点武力才能摆平
Well, I thought the situation
demanded something a little dramatic.
你们是谁？
Who are you people?
我有更好的问题
你是谁？
I would say the better question,
is who are you?
（警戒线 严禁穿越）
合作愉快
To a united front.
你的这种行为
这种友好的假象…
This act of yours,
the imitation of friendship...
别误会，你演技很不错
Don't get me wrong.
You play the part well enough.
我很清楚，因为我也装过
I should know,
having played it myself.
不过当时有段时间
我们之间的亲密关系是真实的
But there was a time when
the affinity between us was quite real.
可不是嘛，然后你就决定
要抢走我所建立的一切
Oh sure, and then you got it
in your head to take what I created.
我检起那枚硬币时，我发誓要效忠你
而不是当你的朋友
When I picked up that coin,
I swore loyalty, Klaus, not friendship.
我会信守诺言
但其余的要靠你自己去争取
I'm holding up my end.
The other one has to be earned.
好吧
Fair enough.
那么我最好把事情真相告诉你
Then you should probably
know the whole story.
这不是我一个人的决定
My decision was not entirely my own.
如果我不夺你的权
If I didn't agree
to usurp your power,
女巫们会杀掉我未出生的孩子
the witches swore to kill
my unborn child.
一开始这孩子对来我说并不重要
At first, the promise of
an offspring meant little to me...
但后来我想起了我父亲
But then I recalled my father,
从我出生那一刻起
他就看不起我
how he held me in contempt
from the moment I was born...
你父亲对你也一样
...as yours did with you.
我不会让发生在我们身上的事
在我的孩子身上
I will not do to my child
what was done to me...
重演
...to us.
所有这些间谍活动，操控别人的行为
All this, the spying,
the manipulation,
都是你被迫去做的吗
that's just something
you were forced into.
是吗？
Is that it?
怎么，你现在感到愧疚了？
And what now,
you feel kind of bad?
“兄弟，我不是针对你”
"Hey, buddy, it's nothing personal."
是吗？
Is that it?
我承认…
I admit...
我嫉妒了
...I was jealous.
我看到你在没有我的情况下
创造了一个王国
I saw the empire you created
on your own without me.
我看到之后，我想要
I saw it, and I wanted it.
你错了，我不是一个人创造的
You're wrong, you know.
I didn't do it on my own.
我当人类的时候
一直活在我父亲的阴影里
I stood in the shadow of my father
my entire human life,
如果不是你，我永远也走不出来
and I never would've gotten out
from under it if not for you.
是你教会了我，人生的路
You're the one who taught me
that a man can't be defined
只有自己说了算
by anyone but himself.
那现在怎么办？
So, what now?
你建立的这个社区
This community that you've built,
你赢得了他们的尊重
you have their respect,
他们的爱戴
their love.
我可以统治他们，但没有你
我得不到人心
I can rule them, but I cannot win them,
not without you.
和我一起统治吧
我们肩并肩
So rule with me side by side,
我们平起平坐
as equals.
作为朋友
Friends.
作为兄弟
Brothers.
你下令诛杀的那些狼人
他们是我的家人
Those werewolves you ordered killed,
that's my family.
刚认的家人吧，亲爱的
Not for long, love.
这些你所谓的家人
I mean,
this so-called family of yours,
他们也没为你做过什么，不是吗？
they haven't done you much good,
have they?
你自己说过
You said it yourself.
他们抛弃了你，让你独自漂泊
They abandoned you,
left you on your own.
现在轮到你抛弃他们了
Now it's simply your turn
to do the same.
也许他们有苦衷
Maybe they had their reasons.
对，我也有苦衷，小狼
Yes, I have reason, too,
little wolf.
如果狼人都死光了
If the werewolves are dead,
吸血鬼就不会那么想要你的命了
then the vampires
have less desire to kill you.
我在努力保护你的安全
I am trying to keep you safe...
看起来你似乎不领情
...not that you appreciate the effort.
等我把孩子生下来后
你会怎么处置我呢？
And as soon as I have this baby,
what happens to me then?
好吧
Right.
我还真是幸运
在你处置我之前，我还有点时间
Well, lucky for me,
I have a little while before I find out.
在此期间，我会找到方法报复你的
And in the meantime,
I will find a way to pay you back for this.
只要我还算是你们家族的一员
你就不能拿我怎么样
As long as I'm in the family way,
you can't do a damn thing about it.
你在找什么？
What are you looking for?
我的小提琴
My violin.
一定是忘在阁楼了
I must've left it in the attic.
那就去拿啊
So just go get it.
不行，我在外面不安全
I can't.
It's not safe for me out there.
有意思，我印象中应该是
大家都怕你吧
Funny, I was under the impression
everyone was afraid of you.
女巫们要抓我
The witches are after me.
你是指那个疯女巫爱格妮丝吗？
You mean, that crazy witch Agnes?
没错，她也想杀我
不过她已经死了
Yeah, she tried to kill me, too.
The thing is, she's dead.
以利亚杀了她
Elijah killed her.
但是…
But...
爱格妮丝是最后一个在世的长老
如果她死了，那我就安全了
Agnes was the last living elder.
If she's dead, then I'm safe.
马赛尔会告诉我的
Marcel would've told me.
也许他不想失去你
这个对抗女巫的秘密武器
Maybe he didn't want to lose his
secret weapon against the witches.
你骗人
You're lying.
我为什么要骗你？
Why would I lie to you?
因为你想利用我
Because you want something from me.
每个人都想利用我
Everyone does.
我想利用你吗？
Do I want something from you?
没错，黛维娜，我是有事要你帮忙
Yeah, Davina. Actually, I do.
多亏了你的好朋友马赛尔
我大多数家人都被下了咒
Thanks to your friend Marcel,
most of my family is cursed.
他们被困于狼形
只有月圆时才能恢复
They're stuck in their wolf form
except on a full moon.
不过我不笨
我知道每个咒语
I'm smart enough
to know that every curse
都有漏洞，而且
has a loophole, and well,
你是我知道最强大的女巫
you're the strongest witch
I've ever heard of.
但我不会骗你来达成我的目的
But I wouldn't lie
to you to get what I want.
我会请求你
I'd ask you.
我想这就是我和马赛尔的差别
I guess that's the difference
between Marcel and me.
在找东西吗？
Looking for something?
我想你搬走后
阁楼一定很安全
I figured with you vacating,
the attic would be a safe zone.
在那找到的
Found this there.
很危险，你不该回来，小约
It was dangerous for
you to come back, Josh.
是没错，不过朋友不就该这么做吗？
Yeah. Well, what are friends for,
or whatever?
嘿，海莉想干嘛？
Hey, what did Hayley want?
你相信她吗？
Do you trust her?
我不知道，怎么了？
I don't know. Why?
她告诉我有个女巫被杀了
She told me about
a witch being killed,
是个女巫长老，但我不知道…
an elder, but I don't know--
是啊，那个疯姿子爱格妮丝
我也听说了
Oh, yeah. Crazy Agnes?
I heard about that.
以利亚暴怒，把她所有的人都杀了
Elijah went all berserker
on her crew.
我猜那场面一定超级恶心
满地的脑袋、内脏
I guess it was super gross,
just, like, heads and guts.
怎么了？
What?
你不是恨那些女巫吗？
You hate the witches.
海莉说得对
Hayley was right.
马赛尔只是在利用我
Marcel is just using me.
小约，我不能待在这里
Josh, I can't stay here.
我不要成为他们的傀儡
你得救我出去
I'm not going to be their puppet.
You have to get me out of here.
好，但你还能去哪里呢？
Okay, but where else
are you going to go?
我浑身都是沼泽的臭味
HAYLEY: I stink of the bog.
活该
谁叫你们之前企图破坏我的统治
Serves you right for your pathetic
attempt to undermine my rule.
尼克，听我说…
Nik, listen--
我下令要把狼人赶尽杀绝
When I order werewolves
to be hunted to extinction,
我希望你们站一边去，看着血流成河
I expect you to stand aside
and let the blood flow.
你还真是民主啊
How delightfully democratic of you.
认出是什么了吗？也许你认不出了
Do you recognize it?
Perhaps you don't.
你上次见到它已经是一千年前了
当时是戴在母亲手上的
It's been 1,000 years since you last
saw it grace the hand of our mother.
这枚戒指是在一个狼人那里找到的
你下令要杀的
The ring was in possession of one
of the very wolves whose extinction
正是这些狼人
you just ordered.
所以我随口问了他几句
So, naturally, I questioned him.
他提到了一个传说
传说在很久以前
He spoke of a legend.
A legend wherein long ago,
他们的首领跟一个强大的女巫
a chief of theirs
had fathered a child
有了孩子
to a very powerful witch.
传说这个孩子，这个男孩
Their mythology further states,
this child, a son,
后来变成了一种
他们宗族从未见过的生物
was later transformed into something
this clan had never before seen.
半狼人半吸血鬼
Something werewolf and vampire.
尼克，我们想补偿你
Nik, we're trying to make amends.
我们找到了你其余的家人
We found remnants of your family.
你亲生父亲的血脉
我们救了他们
The bloodline of your true father,
and we saved them
从你指派去杀他们的吸血鬼手上
from being slaughtered at the hands
of the vampires you command.
尼克劳斯，长久以来
比起家人，你更看重你的野心
Niklaus, your ambitions have come
before this family for far too long.
我恳求你，回家吧
I beseech you, please come home.
什么家？
这间可悲的替代房吗？
What home, this pathetic substitute?
瞧，尽管你们怀疑我
千方百计阻挠我
You see, despite all your doubts,
all you attempts to thwart me,
我还是夺回了我们真正的家
I've reclaimed our true home.
我夺回了整座城市
I took back the entire city.
当你孩子的母亲仍是你的囚徒
You have the audacity
to boast of your victory,
你还要厚颜无耻地吹嘘你的胜利吗？
when the mother of your child
remains your prisoner?
这一切终究还是为了那只美丽的小狼
不是吗，哥哥？
It all comes down to the pretty,
little wolf, doesn't it, brother?
别说了，你们两个
Stop it, both of you.
就算这东西真如你所说
Even if this is what you say it is,
永远陪伴我的家人已经够多了
I have had enough of family
to last me a lifetime.
我何必再自添烦恼呢？
Why would I possibly want any more?
很好，你还没睡
Ah, good. You're awake.
我想请你帮个忙
I have a favor to ask.
我正在为死者祈祷
I am saying prayers for the dead.
希望国王能允许我稍后再为您效劳
I request a moratorium
on favors for the king.
你会喜欢这个请求的
Well, you'll like this one.
我需要你的帮助去保护一些人
It involves helping
people who need protection.
恕我问一句，谁要伤害他们呢？
And whom, may I ask,
do they need protection from?
我
Me.
你知道，最近我曾下令
You see,
I recently ordered the slaughter
屠杀河口地区的狼人
of a group of vagabonds
out in the bayou.
事实证明，我这个决定可能草率了点
Turns out, I may have been too hasty.
问题是，如果吸血鬼们发现
我在保护他们
Thing is, if the vampires
find out I'm protecting them,
这事会引起很大争议
it won't sit well.
我想我可以安排一下
I think I can arrange something.
但我有一个条件
On one condition.
为了我侄女的安全
For her own good,
我想是时候让她离开这里了
I believe it is time for
my niece to leave town.
没关系的，她知道
KLAUS (VOlCE): It's quite all right.
She knows.
- 她知道了？
- 知道你们是吸血鬼吗？
- MARCEL (VOlCE): She does?
-CAMl (VOlCE): That you're vampires?
别担心，他已经魅惑我
一离开就会忘记这一切
Don't worry. He's compelled me to
forget everything as soon as I leave.
你真是锲而不舍
KLAUS: You are tenacious.
这是我最欣赏你的一点
It's one of the things
I like about you.
克劳斯，你不能一直…
Klaus, you can't keep--
但你在寻找一些你根本不想知道的真相
But you're looking for
truths you don't want to find,
怪物还是只在小说中出现比较好
monsters better left as fiction.
该是你离开这里的时候了，卡蜜
It's time for you to
leave this place, Cami.
这是为了你好
For your own good.
你真是个懦夫
You are such a coward.
这不是为了我
This isn't about me.
你强迫我待在这里几个星期
为了让别人，任何人
You have kept me here
for weeks just so someone,
能认清真正的你，而现在我做到了
anyone, would see who you
really are, and now that I have,
这却让你感到害怕，是吗？
it scares the hell out of you,
doesn't it?
如果你真了解我，哪怕只有一点
都足以让你崩溃
If you knew even a fraction of
who I am, it would break you in two.
那就给我看看
Then show me.
尼克劳斯
Niklaus!
好痛啊
It hurts.
他是个野兽
-(ROARlNG)
-He's a beast.
以利亚，压住他
Elijah, hold him down.
哥哥，别让他们这样对我
Brother, please,
don't let them do this to me.
快点啊，儿子，快
Do it now, boy. Now!
救我
Help me.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
没人应该承受这样的经历
No one should have
to experience things like that.
如今你知道的这一切
只会让你招来杀身之祸
Knowing what you do about
this world will only get you killed.
而我不允许这事发生
And I cannot allow that.
离开纽奥良
Leave New Orleans.
忘记所有一切
你今天知道的事
Forget everything
you've learned here today.
忘了我
Forget me.
你没有留在这里的理由
You have no reason to stay.
我没有留在这里的理由
I have no reason to stay.
听着，我现在跟你哥哥处得不错
Look. Things are good
with your brother right now.
他希望我能一起与他统治这里
He wants to run things
with me as partners,
但如果我们继续这样瞒着他见面…
but if we keep meeting like this
behind his back...
你自己说过的
不惜一切代价活下去
You said it yourself,
whatever it takes to stay alive.
所以这只是为了生存，是吗？
如果你在我哥哥面前说谎也如此差劲
This is about survival, is it?
If you were this pathetic a liar
我很惊讶他怎么还没杀了你
with my brother,
I'm surprised he hasn't killed you already.
别这样，蕾贝卡
Come on, Rebekah.
所有爱尼克劳斯的人得到的回报
The only reward anyone ever
gets from loving Niklaus
只有痛苦和死亡
is suffering and death.
你将再一次为他而放弃我
You're choosing him over me,
aren't you?
是吗？
Again.
蕾贝卡，很多人需要我的照顾
Rebekah,
I got people to look out for.
而克劳斯给了我机会这么做
And Klaus is offering me
a chance to do that.
如今我有黛维娜帮我对付女巫
With Davina working her
magic against the witches
还有一个真祖作为盟友
and an Original by my side...
我没法轻易抛弃这一切
...that's not something
I can just turn my back on,
就算是为了你
not even for you.
在你与我哥哥重演历史时
When you were reliving
history with my brother,
你想起过之后的1919年
发生了什么吗？
did you happen to revisit
what came next in 1919,
还是你已经忘记了我们的小秘密？
or have you forgotten
our little secret?
我知道一些话足以让他永远恨你
I know the words that will
make him hate you forever.
在拥抱你的新家人时，别忘了这些
Remember that
when you're embracing your new family.
- 他们是不是…
- 他们安全了
-Are they--
-They're safe.
所有人都是
All of them.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你做的这一切对我来说很重要，以利亚
What you did, Elijah, it means a lot.
- 你该把这个藏好
- 我会的
-You should keep this covered.
-I will.
- 如果让别人看见了…
- 我向你保证
-lf any of the others saw this--
-I promise.
- 我该走了
- 好的
-I should go.
-Right.
不停地数落我有多让你失望
Haven't you had your fill
of telling me all the ways
你都不嫌烦吗，以利亚？
I've disappointed you, Elijah?
有一件很重要的事情我们忘了讨论
Well, there is something important
we neglected to discuss.
我曾指责你对这个孩子有不良居心
I accused you of having ulterior motives
regarding the child.
我错了
I was wrong.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
这些话你一定很难说出口吧
I imagine that must have
been hard for you to say.
爱你是一件很不容易的事，弟弟
You don't make it easy
to love you, brother.
但你却仍固执地这么做
And yet you're obstinate
in your desire to do so.
如果想好了
只要你们愿意
When you're ready,
should you be so inclined...
这里的大门
随时为你和蕾贝卡敞开
...both you and Rebekah
are welcome to join me here.
毕竟这是我们的家
It is, after all, our family home.
卡蜜，我需要你的帮助
Cami, I need your help.
马赛尔一直在骗我，我不能再相信他了
Marcel has been lying to me,
and I can't trust him anymore.
抱歉，我认识你吗？
I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
你被魅惑了
Oh, you've been compelled.
好吧，你要干什么？
Okay. What are you doing?
没事的，我能解除你的魅惑
It's okay. I can fix you.
我很抱歉
这会很痛苦
I'm really sorry,
but this is going to hurt.
片名：创始吸血鬼（第一季）